[SPEAKER_01]: Come on up.
[SPEAKER_01]: This way.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can hear it in your deeper talking.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I bet.
Made it, eh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Success?
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Survival is already success.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good, good, good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Come on, brother.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I see that.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's... we can go around it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not away.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's actually a river.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think we made a mistake.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I think...
[SPEAKER_01]: I think we got to retract our steps.
[SPEAKER_01]: Come on, sonny.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, sit.
[SPEAKER_01]: A day in the mountains.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, there's another one, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was the pond frozen?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
Sunny?
[SPEAKER_00]: Another round of coffee, but it seems that most people are leaving now.
[SPEAKER_01]: When we come back, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Up this way, boy.
It's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sāni mbōe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sāni mbōe.